Guide to the Carol Fennelly papers, 1971-1997 MS2153
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Carol Fennelly papers
1971-1997
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Fennelly, Carol
MS2153
21.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, brochures, videos, films, photographs, newspaper articles, financial records, speeches, and invitations from 1971-1996 relating to the work of homeless rights activist Carol Fennelly and Mitch Snyder as part of the Community for Creative Non-Violence (CCNV).
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
These papers were donated to Gelman Library by Carol Fennelly in 1994.
Biographical Note
Carol Fennelly, a long-time activist, is Director of Hope House. For seventeen years Carol lived and worked at the homeless shelters operated by the Community for Creative Non-Violence. In that capacity she was responsible for the creation of numerous new programs within the organization, including a drop-in center for homeless people, a medical infirmary for 30 homeless men, and recruitment and overall coordination of seven separate organizations which provided services in the 1400 bed Federal City Shelter. Carol is the architect of the Districts "cooling centers" which have saved lives by providing cool places for indigent people during extremely hot weather. She is founder and president of the Trust for Affordable Housing which built over 350 units of Single Room Occupancy Housing for single homeless people in the District of Columbia. In addition, her reputation as an outspoken and effective advocate on issues of concern to homeless people is well known. Along with Mitch Snyder she designed campaigns which won voting rights for homeless people; won passage of the Stewart B. McKinney bill; won passage of the D.C. Right to Overnight Shelter Act; brought a quarter million people to Washington for the Housing Now! March in 1989; and acquired the old Federal City College along with $13 million in renovation funds to create a model shelter in the nation's capitol. She founded Hope House after spending almost a year writing about the plight of families torn apart by the closure of Lorton Prison.
this history came from the Hope House website. http://www.hopehousedc.org/about/about-us.htm
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, brochures, videos, films, photographs, newspaper articles, financial records, speeches, and invitations. This material covers the years 1971-96. This material relates to the work of homeless rights activist Carol Fennelly and Mitch Snyder as part of the Community for Creative Non-Violence (CCNV). CCNV began in the early 1970s as an anti-war group and evolved into an organization that provides food, clothing, shelter, and educational programs for the poor and homeless. Snyder and Fennelly employed non-violent confrontational protest tactics aimed at shocking the public and drawing media attention to the cause of homelessness. A portion of these papers relate to the organizations Housing Now and the Trust for Affordable Housing and the work done on behalf of homeless residents of Washington, D.C.
Collection Organization
Organized into fourteen series: Correspondence, Demonstrations, Ephemera, Entertainment, Financial records, Graphics, Housing, Newspaper articles, Publicity and publications, Speaking engagements, Speeches, Subject files, Video and audio materials, and Oversize materials.
Photographs; Homeless persons; Homelessness -- Washington (D.C.); Washington (D.C.); Housing; Shelters for the homeless; Videotapes; Community for Creative Non-violence (Washington, D.C.); Trust for Affordable Housing; Snyder, Mitch; Sheen, Martin; Fennelly, Carol
- Correspondence, 1971-1993; MS2153 Series 1; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains correspondence. The material dates from 1971-93. This material relates to the work of activist Carol Fennelly primarily related to the issue of the homeless in America. Some of these letters were written by Mitch Snyder during his time in Danbury State Prison from 1971-72.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1)
    General note
  - Correspondence: Mitch Snyder (while in prison), 09/1971-05/1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 06/1985-12/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Hayman Fundraising, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence relates to METRO, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Mitch's strange, interesting, or official letters, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Mitch's strange, interesting, or official letters, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Carol's letters that are interesting or strange, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Carol's letters that are interesting or strange, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Carol's letters that are interesting or strange, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Carol's letters that are interesting or strange, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Demonstrations, 1975-1993; MS2153 Series 2; 0.75 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 5)
  This series contains leaflets, brochures, articles, permit requests, and other publicity materials dated from 1975-93. This material relates to various demonstrations and marches undertaken by Carol Fennelly, Mitch Snyder and the Community for Creative Non-violence. The issues relate to the issue of the homeless.
  - Demonstrations, undated (Box 4)
  - Anti-war March, March First Coalition, 03/01/1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Holy Trinity Church, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Days of Prayer and Resistance at the White House, 06/1981-07/1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Department of the Interior demonstration and camping regulations, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Public gathering Lafayette Park, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rotunda campaign, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Whiteman Air Force Base Carol Fennelly denied access, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Permit for public gathering Lafayette Park, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - March for Shelter, 04/01/1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Harvest of Shame, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Harvest of Shame leaflets, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Harvest of Shame original publicity, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Harvest of Shame arrest sheets, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - permit application for White House and Lafayette Park area, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Demonstrations, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - METRO permit requests, 10/1987-11/1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Nationwide Actions, 07/14/1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Permit application and distribution of literature, 10/31/1988-11/04/1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - American-Soviet Walk, 06/19/1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - White House protest, 06/21/1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NAACP Silent March, 08/26/1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Opposition to budget cuts, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - State of the Union, 01/28/1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Demonstrations, undated (Box 5)
  - Homeless Inagural Ball, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Not dated Call to Prayer arrest book, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Not dated Celebrity Petition, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Not dated METRO, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Not dated Information about civil disobedience and the D.C. Superior Court and Jail, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Ephemera, undated; MS2153 Series 3; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 7)
  This series contains one set of clothing worn by Martin Sheen during the making of the movie "Samaritan" about the life and work of Mitch Snyder. The other items in this series are plaques related to the work of Mitch Snyder.
  - Ephemera, undated (Box 6)
  - Clothing worn by Martin Sheen during making of the movie "Samaritan" about the life and work of Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ephemera, undated (Box 7)
  - Plaques and awards for Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Entertainment, 1984-1993; MS2153 Series 4; 1 Linear feet (Box 8, Box 9)
  This series contains scripts, television show documents, and movie premiere documents. This material mostly relates to the production of the movie "Samaritan" about the life of Mitch Snyder. There is also material related to a 60 Minutes television episode from 1993 and other television projects. This material is dated from 1984-93.
  - Entertainment, undated (Box 8)
  - 60 Minutes television show, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "The Confessional" a play by Jonathan Englert, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Counter Talk television show, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "Love Mary" movie script first draft, 12/05/1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "People on a no-way street" KYW Newsradio 1060, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Promises to Keep" movie, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Race Against Winter" movie script second draft, 12/16/1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "The Recovery" movie script, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Samaritan The Mitch Snyder Story" movie premiere, 05/12/1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Samaritan. .", 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Samaritan.. ." script first draft, 06/27/1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Entertainment, undated (Box 9)
  - "Samaritan.. ." script second draft, 12/16/1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Samaritan... " CCNV rights to a proposal for a movie, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Voices from the Street "Beauty and the Beast" play, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Financial records, 1988-1993; MS2153 Series 5; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 10)
  This series contains financial records related to the Community for Creative Non-Violence including budgets and fundraising. This material covers the years 1988-93.
  - Financial records, undated (Box 10)
  - Auction benefit, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Auction Hard Rock Café, 11/12/1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CCNV Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - CCNV Budget, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CCNV Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CCNV Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Budget St. Francis Residence, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Donations, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fundraiser Bartender's Ball, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Organization Hayman Business System, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Grants from Tides Foundation and Morris and Gwendolyn Cafritz Foundation, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Income Taxes of Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Taxes refusal to pay taxes on telephone service, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Graphics, 1979-1993; MS2153 Series 6; 1 Linear feet (Box 12, Box 11)
  This series contains photographs and negatives. This material dates from 1979-93.
  - Graphics, undated (Box 11)
  - Celebrities, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Celebrities, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Hearings, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Lunch Hunger in the Land of Plenty, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Demonstration 12th St., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Demonstration and arrest at the White House Call to Prayer, 06/17/1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Demonstration Giant Sit-in, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Demonstration Hands Across America, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Demonstration Initiative 17, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Demonstration Kansas City, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Demonstration outside Labor Department, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Demonstration March on White House April 1 (prints and negatives), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Demonstration at National Archives, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Demonstration People's State of the Union, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Demonstration Pray-ins, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Demonstration against Reagan's budgets, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Demonstration Reagan Ville II (photos taken by Mary Ellen Hombs), undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Demonstrations White House and Labor Department, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Demonstrations unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Entertainment "Samaritan", undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Graphics, undated (Box 12)
  - Fasts of Mitch Snyder Corpus Christi, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Group images (negatives), undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Holidays Christmas (negatives), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Holidays Christmas (negatives), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Holidays Christmas contact sheets, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Holidays Thanksgiving, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Holidays Thanksgiving and other images, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Housing Now Ted Kennedy function, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Housing Now Yard Sale fundraiser, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Homeless Inaugural Ball, 01/19/1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (negatives), undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (prints), undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous community images, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Pepper's photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Shelter 1361 Fairmont, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Shelter images (prints and negatives), undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Shelter early images, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Snyder, Mitch, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Housing, 1984-1997; MS2153 Series 7; 6.75 Linear feet (Box 13, Box 15, Box 14, Box 17, Box 16, Box 12A, Box 22, Box 23, Box 20, Box 21, Box 18, Box 19)
  This series contains bills, articles, campaign literature, correspondence, financial records, agendas and meeting minutes, and press releases. This material dates from 1984-97. Much of this material relates to work of the group the Trust for Affordable Housing and the operation and renovation of the homeless shelter at 425 2nd St.
  - Housing, undated (Box 12A)
  - Affordable Housing Act: Bill, undated (Box 12A, Folder 1)
  - Affordable Housing Act: Congressional Response to the AHA, undated (Box 12A, Folder 2)
  - Affordable Housing Act: Craig's legislative program, undated (Box 12A, Folder 3)
  - Affordable Housing Act: HR 4990, undated (Box 12A, Folder 4)
  - Affordable Housing Act: National priority fact sheet, undated (Box 12A, Folder 5)
  - Affordable Housing Act: Miscellaneous documents, 1988 (Box 12A, Folder 6)
  - Affordable Housing Act: Press Release, 1988 (Box 12A, Folder 7)
  - Affordable Housing Act: Summary, Release HR 973, 1989 (Box 12A, Folder 8)
  - Housing: Acts for permanent housing assistance for homeless, undated (Box 12A, Folder 9)
  - Housing: CCNV working paper on low-income housing, 1987 (Box 12A, Folder 10)
  - Housing: Community trusts for affordable housing, 1984 (Box 12A, Folder 11)
  - Housing: Congressional Research Service report on low-income housing, undated (Box 12A, Folder 12)
  - Housing: House Resolution 558, undated (Box 12A, Folder 13)
  - Housing: Institute for Policy studies Affordable Housing Program, undated (Box 12A, Folder 14)
  - Housing: Leland Act draft, undated (Box 12A, Folder 15)
  - Housing: Letters invitation to join the call for affordable housing, undated (Box 12A, Folder 16)
  - Housing: National Community Housing Partnership Act 1987 Hale and Dorr draft (Box 12A, Folder 17)
  - Housing: Notes (handwritten), undated (Box 12A, Folder 18)
  - Housing: Press release Housing shortage study and Washington Post article, 04/1989 (Box 12A, Folder 19)
  - Housing: Press release take-off the boards [07/14] and Housing: A National Priority, undated (Box 12A, Folder 20)
  - Housing: Mitch Snyder documents, undated (Box 12A, Folder 21)
  - Housing Now: Articles of Incorporation and IRS documentation, undated (Box 12A, Folder 22)
  - Housing Now: Campaign press article, 1988 (Box 12A, Folder 23)
  - Housing Now: Celebrity Yard Sale fundraiser, undated (Box 12A, Folder 24)
  - Housing Now: Curriculum, undated (Box 12A, Folder 25)
  - Housing Now: Endorsement form, undated (Box 12A, Folder 26)
  - Housing, undated (Box 13)
  - Housing Now: Celebrity lists, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Housing Now: Key Contacts, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Housing Now: Contacts from different regions, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Housing Now: Correspondence, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Housing Now: Demonstration, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Housing Now: Endorsement list, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Housing Now: Executive Committee meetings, 05/1989-09/1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Housing Now: Financing, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Housing Now: Flyers, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Housing Now: Fundraiser Casey Kames, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Housing Now: History, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Housing Now: Hollywood Committee, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Housing Now: Legislative issues, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Housing Now: Lists, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Housing Now: March and articles about it, 10/07/1989-10/08/1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Housing Now: March analysis, 10/07/1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Housing Now: March -Children's, 03/1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Housing Now: March and fundraiser, 10/1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Housing Now: March Candidates for "Real People" speakers, 10/07/1989 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Housing Now: New York City meeting list, 02/05/1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Housing, undated (Box 14)
  - Housing Now: Meetings, 02/1989-08/1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Housing Now: Miscellaneous documents, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Housing Now: National Steering Committee, 1989 03/1989-07/1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Housing Now: Newsletters August, 09/11/1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Housing Now: Notes for card files, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Housing Now: Organizations contact 1st campaign meeting, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Housing Now: Outreach committees, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Housing Now: Permit applications, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Housing Now: Press releases, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Housing Now: Program committee, 08/22/1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Housing Now: Publicity PSA, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Housing Now: Raw notes for Housing Now, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Housing Now: Raw notes for Housing Now, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Housing Now: Raw notes for Housing Now, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Housing Now: Tax information, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Housing Now: T-Shirt production, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Housing, undated (Box 15)
  - Housing Now: "Housing and Homelessness: A Teaching Guide", undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Housing Now: Travel notes on Housing Now travels, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Housing Now: Travel Midwest trip, 06/1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Housing Now: Travel Southern trip, 04/1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Housing Now: Travel Campaign schedule, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Housing Now: Union lists, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Housing, undated (Box 16)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St., undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Barred List, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Interim floor plan for drop-in center, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Emergency repairs, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. FCC eviction Robbins vs. Reagan, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Fullerton Statement (Anne Fullerton volunteer at Women's Shelter), undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Grand opening, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Grievance committee process, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. License mgt. agreement, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. meeting attendance list [03/31/??], undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. "memorandum of Agreement" [05/21/??], undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Original lease, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. Original shelter donor list and leaflet, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Housing, undated (Box 17)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St.renovations all phase construction bid, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations correspondence to Mitch, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations CCNV's design, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations demolition plans, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations meeting with Sue Marshall, 05/27/1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations "scope of work" Levenson papers, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations testimony by Mitch, 10/29/1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Shelter: 425 2nd St. renovations, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Shelter: Shelter census city operated or contracted adult shelters daily census, 05/1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Shelter: Daily census report, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Housing, undated (Box 18)
  - Shelter: Church based temporary shelter program, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Shelter: D.C. Emergency shelter, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Shelter: Assorted shelter housing materials, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Shelter: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Shelter: Mitch's proposal for Pierce/Blair shelters, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Shelter: Use of Nichols School as emergency shelter, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Shelter: Night Hospitality program, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Shelter: Night Hospitality program, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Shelter: Westat (an employee and research corporation survey of managers of shelters for homeless, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Shelter: Women's shelter log Women's hospitality, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Shelter: Women's Shelter, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Housing, undated (Box 19)
  - Anchor Mental Health, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Anna Cooper House, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Anna Cooper House, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Anna Cooper House, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing proposal and 1992 annual report (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Annual report, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing annual report, 12/1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing annual reports, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing annual report and meeting minutes, 12/1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing architect replacement, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing miscellaneous art work, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing articles of incorporation, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing audit, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Bell Atlantic phone calls in question, 10/24/1991 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors meeting, 02/11/1997 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Housing, undated (Box 20)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Trust for Affordable Housing Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)